<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AllAroundClemson</string>
    <string name="profileTitle">Profile</string>
    <string name="mapTitle">Campus Map</string>
    <string name="sportsTitle">Sports</string>
    <string name="gameTitle">Trivia Game</string>

    <string name="homeTeam">Clemson</string>
    <string name="awayTeam">Opponent</string>
    <string name="homeScore">0</string>
    <string name="awayScore">0</string>

    <string name="penaltyHolder">penalty</string>
    <string name="penaltyDesc">%1$s:\n%2$s</string>
    <string-array name="penalty_name">
        <item>Blocking below the waist</item>
        <item>Block in the back</item>
        <item>Chop block</item>
        <item>Clipping</item>
        <item>Contacting the kicker</item>
        <item>Delay of game</item>
        <item>Encroachment</item>
        <item>Equipment violation</item>
        <item>Face mask</item>
        <item>False start</item>
        <item>Helmet-to-helmet collision</item>
        <item>Helping the runner</item>
        <item>Holding</item>
        <item>Horse-collar tackle</item>
        <item>Illegal batting</item>
        <item>Illegal formation</item>
        <item>Illegal forward pass</item>
        <item>Illegal hands to the face</item>
        <item>Illegal kick</item>
        <item>Illegal kickoff</item>
        <item>Illegal motion</item>
        <item>Illegal participation/Too many players</item>
        <item>Illegal shift</item>
        <item>Illegal substitution/Too many players in the formation</item>
        <item>Illegal touching of a forward pass</item>
        <item>Illegal touching of a free kick</item>
        <item>Illegal touching of a scrimmage kick</item>
        <item>Illegal use of hands</item>
        <item>Ineligible receiver downfield</item>
        <item>Intentional grounding</item>
        <item>Leaping</item>
        <item>Leverage</item>
        <item>Neutral Zone Infraction</item>
        <item>Offside</item>
        <item>Offside pass</item>
        <item>Pass interference</item>
        <item>Personal foul</item>
        <item>Punt out of bounds</item>
        <item>Rough play</item>
        <item>Roughing the passer</item>
        <item>Roughing the kicker</item>
        <item>Roughing the snapper</item>
        <item>Running into the kicker</item>
        <item>Sideline infraction</item>
        <item>Spearing</item>
        <item>Targeting</item>
        <item>Time count violation</item>
        <item>Tripping</item>
        <item>Unsportsmanlike conduct</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="penalty_description">
        <item>An illegal block, from any direction, below the waist by any defensive player or
            by an offensive player under certain situations, by any player after change of
            possession, by any player in high school with certain exceptions. Sometimes incorrectly
            referred to as a "chop block".</item>
        <item>A blocker contacting a non-ballcarrying member of the opposing team from behind and
            above the waist.</item>
        <item>An offensive player tries to cut block a defensive player that is already being
            blocked by another offensive player. The second block may need to be below the thigh
            or knee, depending on the code.	</item>
        <item>A blocker contacting a non-ballcarrying opponent from behind and at or below the waist
        </item>
        <item>Any contact with the kicker when in the act of kicking, unless the ball has touched
            the ground (as in a bad snap), the defender touches the ball, contact by a blocker
            causes the contact, or the contact is slight or incidental.	</item>
        <item>Any action which delays the next play.</item>
        <item>Before the snap, a defensive player illegally crosses the line of scrimmage
            and makes contact with an opponent or has a clear path to the quarterback.</item>
        <item>Any player in the game without necessary safety equipment.</item>
        <item>Grasping the face mask of another player while attempting to block or tackle him.
        </item>
        <item>An offensive player illegally moves after lining up for, but prior to, the snap.
        </item>
        <item>The act of hitting another player\'s helmet with your own.</item>
        <item>When a member of the offensive or receiving team pushes, pulls, grasps, or lifts a
            person in possession of the ball.</item>
        <item>Illegally grasping or pulling an opponent other than the ball carrier while attempting
        to ward off a block or cover a receiver.</item>
        <item>Illegally tackling another player by grabbing the inside of the ball carrier\'s
        shoulder pads or jersey from behind and yanking the player down.</item>
        <item>Any intentional batting of a loose ball or ball in player possession.</item>
        <item>Less than seven players on the line of scrimmage at the snap of the ball.</item>
        <item>A forward pass that is thrown from past the line of scrimmage.</item>
        <item>Pushing or hitting a player on offense in the head or helmet.</item>
        <item>Any ball not kicked in accordance with the rules, for instance:\n
            \u2022 When an attempted drop kick bounces more than once before being kicked.\n
            \u2022 When a player kicks the ball after a turnover.\n
            \u2022 When a player kicks the ball after having advanced the ball past the line of
            scrimmage.
        </item>
        <item>The ball, after a kickoff, heads out of bounds between both goal lines without
        touching any player on either team.</item>
        <item>A player in motion is moving forward at the time of the snap.</item>
        <item>Twelve or more players participate during the play</item>
        <item>A player is not in motion but is not set before the snap.</item>
        <item>The offense has twelve or more players in the huddle for a period of 3-5 seconds
        or twelve or more players are in the formation before a play.</item>
        <item>A forward pass first touches an ineligible receiver. If the ball is touched by the
        defense first, any player may touch it.</item>
        <item>The ball, after the free kick, first touches a member of the kicking team prior to
        travelling ten yards.</item>
        <item>The ball, during the scrimmage kick, is touched by a kicking team player, unless
        the kick is touched by the receiving team or another member of the kicking team.</item>
        <item>Illegal use of the hands against a player on offense while attempting to ward off a
        block, cover a receiver, or tackle a ball carrier.</item>
        <item>An ineligible receiver is past the line of scrimmage prior to a forward pass.</item>
        <item>A forward pass is thrown intentionally incomplete so that the pass avoids loss of
            yardage or to conserve time.</item>
        <item>A defender at least one yard in front of the line of scrimmage running forward and
        leaping in an attempt to block a field goal or a point-after tries to land on other players
        on either team.</item>
        <item>A defensive player jumping or standing on a teammate or an opponent to block
        or attempt to block an opponent\'s kick.</item>
        <item>Before the snap, a defensive player jumps into the neutral zone and "startles" an
        offensive player, causing him to false start</item>
        <item>A player is on the wrong side of the line of scrimmage when the ball is snapped.
        </item>
        <item>Any act to direct the ball forward other than a kick or a forward pass.</item>
        <item>Making physical contact with an intended receiver, after the ball has been thrown
        and before it has been touched by another player, in order to hinder or prevent him from
        catching a forward pass.</item>
        <item>Any conduct or safety related infraction. Could include unnecessary roughness, or
            "piling on" a ball carrier who is already down.</item>
        <item>A scrimmage kick goes out of bounds in flight untouched by the receiving team
        between the 20 yard lines.</item>
        <item>A flagrant conduct- or safety-infraction. Includes fighting, punching, and intentional
        contact with an official.</item>
        <item>A defender continues an effort to tackle or "hit" a passer after the passer has
        already thrown a pass.</item>
        <item>A defender, having missed an attempt to block a kick, tackles the kicker or otherwise
            runs into the kicker in a way that might injure the kicker or his vulnerable extended
            kicking leg.</item>
        <item>On a punt or field goal attempt, the long snapper is allowed to regain his balance
            and assume a protective position before he is contacted by the defense.</item>
        <item>On a kicking play where the defense fails to touch the kicked ball, the defense runs
            into the kicker/punter.</item>
        <item>A player is outside of the team box, a coach is outside of the coaches\' box, or too
        many coaches are in the coaches\' box.</item>
        <item>Tackling or otherwise contacting an opponent with one\'s helmet.</item>
        <item>A defensive player tackles with the crown of his helmet, by initiating contact to the
        opponent\'s head above the player\'s neck.</item>
        <item>On offense, failing to snap the ball before the play clock reaches zero. Delay of game
        </item>
        <item>A player trips another play with the lower leg</item>
        <item>Any person acts or speaks in a manner deemed to be intentionally harmful or especially
            objectionable by the game officials, or by rule. Unsportsmanlike conduct is a non-contact
            foul; if contact is involved it becomes a personal foul.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>